

Profile

To my technical knowledge I can include: Selenium on JS with Mocha, WebdriverIO, React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery. Have experience with works users interfaces Bootstrap, Semantic UI. There is also knowledge and understanding of the OOP, the initial knowledge of programming in Java. Familiar with the MySQL database. Knowledge of the theory of software testing. Familiar with the GitHub version control system.

Employment History

QA at «uTest»

February 2017 - March 2019

Freelance testing of web pages, mobile applications and desktop applications

Master of KPPiA at LLC "M-Qadro"

February 2016 - October 2016

Installation of equipment of automated production lines

Engineer of the brigade of telecommunication networks at Atracom Ltd., Kiev

December 2015 - February 2016

Internet connection

Connection to the telephone network

Content Manager at Oasis water LLC, Kiev

February 2013 - September 2013

Courses

Front-End JavaScript Online Summer 2019, EPAM

June 2019 - August 2019

Education

Master, computer-integrated technological processes and production, Kyiv National University of Technology and Design, Kiev

September 2010 - January 2017

About me

In addition to the basic skills for work, I have such qualities as creative thinking towards the realization of the tasks set, I am not afraid to take responsibility, speed of learning, ability to find a common language with other people.

Details

0933029243

yurilev4@gmail.com

Links

Telegram GitHub

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

React

Redux

GitHub

Webdriver IO

Java

Selenium